[DOOR SLAMS]
(Mrs Cooper:)You don't hunt, do you?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
(Mrs Cooper(entering):)Good morning, Snickerdoodle.
(Mrs Cooper(entering):)- Morning.
- Oh.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, that looks awful fancy.
What is that?
(Sheldon:)It's my idea of what DNA would look like
in a silicon-based life form.
(Mrs Cooper:)But intelligently designed
by a creator, right?
(Sheldon:)What do you want, Mom?
(Mrs Cooper:)You know how your daddy used to say
that you can only fish for so long...
...before you gotta throw
a stick of dynamite in the water?
- Yeah?
- Well, I'm done fishing.
- You put those on.
- What for?
Because you're gonna go
to your office...
...apologize to your boss
and get your job back.
(Sheldon:)- No.
- I'm sorry.